asknlearn.com 2016-04-14

# Wizlearn Technologies

### Wizlearn Data Privacy Policy

  1. Our permissions policy
  2. We do not rent or purchase lists
  3. No old lists, either
  4. Keeping your personal information
  5. Protecting your data
  6. Adhering to the Data Privacy Principles
  7. When Wizlearn sends emails to you
  8. Ensuring secure billing transactions
  9. In summary

#### 9 things you need to know

At Wizlearn, we're dedicated to protecting your privacy and the privacy of anyone on the receiving end of a Wizlearn-delivered email. To that end, we have instituted certain policies - rules, you might call them - to help us make sure Wizlearn remains a safe, trusted environment for email marketing and correspondence. Here, we outline those policies and our efforts to enforce them.  

#### 1\. Our permissions policy

Wizlearn practises permission-based communications. We send emails to people who want to receive those emails. Wizlearn's permission policy is part of the Terms of Use agreed to by every Wizlearn customer, and it appears as a reminder every time we communicate with prospects/clients. It goes beyond the stipulations set forth in the Singapore legislation and is as follows:

To send an email to someone using Wizlearn, that recipient must be:

  * Someone who is a customer, member or subscriber of our organization,
  * Someone who has specifically asked to receive our emails by opting in or signing up, or
  * Someone who has bought a product or service from us in the past 18 months
  * Someone who has enquired for service and agreed to be on our list

#### 2\. No list rental or purchasing here

We do not rent, sell, or otherwise share our lists or those of our customers, and we do not allow any partner/ customer to rent or purchase lists.  

#### 3\. No old lists, either

That's why we don't allow sending to any email address that was obtained more than 24 months ago and has not received any correspondence from us since that time. When it comes to sending permission-based email, the age of the list matters. If enough time passes between someone initially subscribing to your list and eventually receiving an email from you, permission "expires" as people eventually forget what they've signed up for.   

#### 4\. Keeping your personal information

In order to create and administer your Wizlearn account, we explicitly ask for and collect certain information about you and your company, including financial information used to verify identity and bill for services. Under no circumstances will we share your (or any other member's) personal information with any third party, except local authorities.

We also collect certain aggregate information about our customers. We use this information to improve our services and to do a better job of marketing them. We may also report such information -- always in aggregate form¹ and never in a way that could identify individuals -- to third parties, such as newspapers or industry observers or potential customers and partners. 

#### 5\. Protecting your data

We do everything we can to make sure your email content and response data remains private and confidential. Though we reserve the right to monitor your lists, content and response data from time to time to make sure they comply with our Terms of Use, we will never share, sell or rent your customer data to anyone for any reason.   

#### 6\. Adhering to the Data Privacy Principles

Wizlearn adheres to the data privacy principles as set forth by the Singapore government. These policies are designed to provide adequate protection for personal data collected, used and retained.

Direct any Data Privacy inquiries or requests to: 

_**Wizlearn Technologies Pte Ltd  
10 Science Park Road #03-13 Singapore 117684 ** _

#### 7\. When Wizlearn sends emails to you

Just as we ask and expect you to respect the inbox of your customers, we will do our best to respect yours. The only emails you'll receive from us will be emails related to your account or your use of Wizlearn / Asknlearn™. We might alert you to new features or site enhancements. We might check in to see how your last learning went. Some of those emails may be directed to everyone, and some of them may be written just for you. In the future, we may also ask if you'd like to receive information from our partners. We do not yet have partners, and until we do, we will not ask.  

#### 8\. Ensuring secure billing transactions

You may be asked to supply certain credit card and billing information in order to purchase Wizlearn services. That information is transferred, using the most secure transmission technology, to a trusted third party for processing. The information is then encrypted using Microsoft Encryption standards and securely stored to handle your transactions. Your credit card information is not stored on the Wizlearn website or in our database. We do not have access to your credit card information.  

#### 9\. To sum things up...

Your privacy, and the privacy of people on both sides of Wizlearn emails, is extremely important to us, and we'll do everything we can to protect it. Direct any questions you may have regarding this Privacy Policy to [sales@wizlearn.com](mailto:sales@wizlearn.com). And if you suspect our privacy and permission policy has been abused in any way, please call us at +65 6776 2013. 

¹ ‘aggregate form’ means stripping personal details but retaining demographic data and relevant data that helps us analyse buyer behaviour
